Guide to the Yale College Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Horace Taft as dean, 1963-1979; Accession 1984-A-030
  - Subject File, Series I
    - 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - U.S. Grant (Box 20, Folder 268)
      - Veterans Benefits (Box 20, Folder 269)
      - Visitors (Box 20, Folder 270)
      - Women at Yale (Box 20, Folder 271 - 272)
      - Y.C.D.O. Openings (Box 20, Folder 273)
      - Yale College Program of Study (Box 20, Folder 274)
    - 1975-1976
      - Administrative Science Major (Box 21, Folder 275)
      - Admissions, Undergraduate (Box 21, Folder 276)
      - Admissions, Faculty Advisory Committee on (Box 21, Folder 277)
      - Affirmative Action (Box 21, Folder 278)
      - Affirmative Action -- Approvals (Box 21, Folder 279)
      - Afro-American Cultural Center (Box 21, Folder 280)
      - Afro-American Studies Committee (Box 21, Folder 281)
      - Alumni (Box 21, Folder 282)
      - American Council on Education (Box 21, Folder 283)
      - American Studies (Box 21, Folder 284)
      - Anthropology (Box 21, Folder 285)
      - Applications for Positions (Box 22, Folder 286)
      - Applied Mathematics (Box 22, Folder 287)
      - Appointment Procedures (Box 22, Folder 288)
      - Appointments Committee, Junior (Box 22, Folder 289)
      - Appointments Committee, Senior
        - Biological Sciences (Box 22, Folder 290)
        - Humanities (Box 22, Folder 291)
        - Physical Sciences (Box 22, Folder 292)
        - Social Sciences (Box 22, Folder 293)
      - Architecture (Box 22, Folder 294)
      - Art School and Art Major (Box 22, Folder 295)
      - Association of Colleges in New England (Box 23, Folder 296)
      - Astronomy (Box 23, Folder 297)
      - Athletics (Box 23, Folder 298)
      - Band (Box 23, Folder 299)
      - Benefits (Box 23, Folder 300)
      - Biology (Box 23, Folder 301)
      - Buildings and Grounds (Box 23, Folder 302)
      - Bursar (Box 23, Folder 303)
      - Calendar (Box 23, Folder 304)
      - Canadian Studies (Box 23, Folder 305)
      - Campus Police (Box 23, Folder 306)
      - Career Advisory (Box 23, Folder 309 - 310)
      - Career Development Awards (Box 23, Folder 311)
      - Chairmanships (Box 24, Folder 312)
      - Chaplain (Box 24, Folder 313)
      - Chemistry (Box 24, Folder 314)
      - Classics (Box 24, Folder 315)
      - College Entrance Examination Board (Box 24, Folder 316)
      - Combined Science Major (Box 24, Folder 317)
      - Commencement (Box 24, Folder 318)
      - Committees -- Standing and Special (Box 24, Folder 319)
      - Communications, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 320)
      - Comparative Literature (Box 24, Folder 321)
      - Computers at Yale (Box 24, Folder 322)
      - Computer Science (Box 24, Folder 323)
      - Concilium (Box 24, Folder 324)
      - Concilium -- Annual Report (Box 24, Folder 325)
      - Conferences (Box 24, Folder 326)
      - Continuing Education (Box 24, Folder 327)
      - Co-op (Box 24, Folder 328)
      - Corporation Actions (Box 24, Folder 329)
      - Corporation -- Minutes and Bylaws (Box 24, Folder 330)
      - Council of Masters (Box 25, Folder 331)
      - Council, Yale College (Box 25, Folder 332)
      - Council, University (Box 25, Folder 333)
      - Course Credits (Box 25, Folder 334)
      - Course of Study (Box 25, Folder 335 - 336)
      - Course of Study (Box 26, Folder 337)
      - Course of Study Committee -- Yale College (Box 26, Folder 338 - 339)
      - Dance (Box 26, Folder 340)
      - Davenport (Box 26, Folder 342)
      - Deans, College (Box 26, Folder 343)
      - Deans, College -- Applications (Box 26, Folder 344)
      - Deans' Conferences (Box 26, Folder 345)
      - Development Office (Box 26, Folder 346)
      - Dining Hall (Box 26, Folder 347)
      - Distributional Requirements (Box 26, Folder 348)
      - Divinity School (Box 26, Folder 349)
      - DUS -- General (Director of Undergraduate Studies) (Box 26, Folder 350)
      - Dwight Hall (Box 26, Folder 351)
      - Early Concentration (Box 26, Folder 352)
      - East Asian Languages and Literatures (Box 26, Folder 353)
      - Economics (Box 27, Folder 354)
      - Engineering and Applied Science (Box 27, Folder 355)
      - English (Box 27, Folder 356)
      - Examinations (Box 27, Folder 357)
      - Executive Committee (Box 27, Folder 358 - 359)
      - Faculty -- Yale College (Box 27, Folder 360)
      - Faculty Advising (Box 27, Folder 361)
      - Faculty Club (Box 27, Folder 362)
      - Faculty Meetings (Box 27, Folder 363)
      - Faculty Meetings, Yale College: Agendas, Minutes, Supporting Material (Box 27, Folder 364)
      - Faculty Problems (Box 27, Folder 365)
      - Family Rights and Privacy Act (Box 28, Folder 366)
      - Fellowships (Box 28, Folder 367)
      - Film Committee (Box 28, Folder 368)
      - Financial Aid (Box 28, Folder 369)
      - Foreign Students (Box 28, Folder 370)
      - French (Box 28, Folder 372)
      - Freshmen (Box 28, Folder 373)
      - Freshmen Counselors (Box 28, Folder 374)
      - Freshman Reallocation (Box 28, Folder 375)
      - The Generic Pronoun (Box 28, Folder 376)
      - Geology and Geophysics (Box 28, Folder 377)
      - German (Box 28, Folder 378)
      - Gimbel Cup (Box 28, Folder 379)
      - Glee Club (Box 28, Folder 380)
      - Governance (Box 28, Folder 381)
      - Grading (Box 28, Folder 382)
      - Graduate School (Box 28, Folder 383)
      - Grant and Contract Administration (Box 28, Folder 384)
      - Guggenheim Fellowships (Box 28, Folder 385)
      - Hatch Prize (Box 28, Folder 386)
      - Health Services, Yale (Box 28, Folder 387)
      - History (Box 29, Folder 388)
      - History of Art (Box 29, Folder 389)
      - History of Science and Medicine (Box 29, Folder 390)
      - Honors and Special Projects (Box 29, Folder 391)
      - Honorary Degrees (Box 29, Folder 392)
      - Housing (Box 29, Folder 393)
      - Human Subjects (Box 29, Folder 394)
      - Humanities, Council on (Box 29, Folder 395)
      - Humanities, National Endowment for the (Box 29, Folder 396)
      - Humanities Institute (Box 29, Folder 397)
      - Humanities, Special Courses in (Box 29, Folder 398)
      - Humanities Council, Connecticut (Box 29, Folder 399)
      - Industrial Relations (Box 29, Folder 400)
      - Information, Public (Box 29, Folder 401)
      - Institutional Research, Office of (Box 29, Folder 402)
      - Institute for Educational Management (Box 29, Folder 403)
      - Institute for Social end Policy Studies (Box 29, Folder 404)
      - Internship Programs (Box 29, Folder 405)
      - Invitations (Box 29, Folder 406)
      - Italian (Box 29, Folder 407)
      - Job Opportunities (Box 29, Folder 408)
      - Joint Committee on Combined B.A.-M.A. (Box 30, Folder 409)
      - Joint Council of Social Chairmen (Box 30, Folder 410)
      - Junior Year Abroad (Box 30, Folder 411)
      - Language Committee, University (Box 30, Folder 412)
      - Language Institute, Summer (Box 30, Folder 413)
      - Law School (Box 30, Folder 414)
      - Leaves of Absence
        - Faculty (Box 30, Folder 415)
        - Junior Faculty (Box 30, Folder 416)
        - Materials (Box 30, Folder 417)
        - Requests (Box 30, Folder 418 - 419)
        - Students (Box 30, Folder 420)
      - Lecturers, Part-time (Box 30, Folder 421)
      - Legal Advisor (Box 30, Folder 422)
      - Legal Studies (Box 30, Folder 423)
      - Letters -- general (Box 30, Folder 424)
      - Library (Box 30, Folder 425)
      - Linguistics (Box 30, Folder 426)
      - Literature Major (Box 30, Folder 427)
      - Loan Policy, Student (Box 30, Folder 428)
      - Mathematics (Box 31, Folder 429)
      - MEChA (Box 31, Folder 430)
      - Media Design Studio (Box 31, Folder 431)
      - Medical School (Box 31, Folder 432)
      - Minority Recruitment (Box 31, Folder 433)
      - Minorities -- Status of (Box 31, Folder 434)
      - Molecular Biochemistry and Biophysics (Box 31, Folder 435)
      - Morse Committee (Box 31, Folder 438)
      - Music (Box 31, Folder 439)
      - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures (Box 31, Folder 440)
      - New Haven High Schools Programs (Box 31, Folder 441 - 442)
      - Nobel Prizes (Box 31, Folder 443)
      - Office on the Education of Women (Box 31, Folder 444)
      - Faculty Offices in Colleges (Box 31, Folder 445)
      - Organization and Management, School of (Box 31, Folder 446)
      - Parents' Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 447)
      - Parking (Box 32, Folder 448)
      - Performing Arts (Box 32, Folder 449)
      - Personnel (Box 32, Folder 450)
      - Phi Beta Kappa (Box 32, Folder 451)
      - Philosophy (Box 32, Folder 452)
      - Physics (Box 32, Folder 453)
      - Poland (Box 32, Folder 454)
      - Political Union (Box 32, Folder 455)
      - Political Science (Box 32, Folder 456)
      - Pre-Medical Advisory (Box 32, Folder 457)
      - PREP (Summer Transitional Program) (Box 32, Folder 458)
      - Pre-Registration and "W's" (Box 32, Folder 459)
      - President's Office (Box 32, Folder 460)
      - Prize Essay (Box 32, Folder 461)
      - Prize Teaching Fellows (Box 32, Folder 462)
      - Prizes, Undergraduate (Box 33, Folder 463)
      - PROP (Pre-registration Orientation Program) (Box 33, Folder 464)
      - Provost's Office (Box 33, Folder 465)
      - Psychology (Box 33, Folder 466)
      - Publication Series, Yale College (Box 33, Folder 467)
      - Puerto Rico -- Courses and Personnel (Box 33, Folder 468)
      - Readmission (Box 33, Folder 469)
      - Rebate Policy (Box 33, Folder 470)
      - Registrar's Office (Box 33, Folder 471)
      - Religious Studies (Box 33, Folder 472)
      - Resident Fellow Requests (Box 33, Folder 473)
      - Reunions (Box 33, Folder 474)
      - ROTC (Box 33, Folder 475)
      - Safety (Box 33, Folder 476)
      - Science and Engineering Association, Yale (Box 33, Folder 477)
      - Scholars of the House (Box 33, Folder 478)
      - Secretary's Office (Box 33, Folder 479)
      - Security (Box 33, Folder 480)
      - Slavic (Box 33, Folder 481)
      - Sociology (Box 33, Folder 482)
      - Space (Box 33, Folder 483)
      - Spanish (Box 33, Folder 484)
      - Spanish Department Letters (Box 33, Folder 485)
      - Special Committee on Yale College (Box 33, Folder 486)
      - Special Programs (Box 33, Folder 487)
      - Yale Station (Box 33, Folder 488)
      - Steering Committee (Box 33, Folder 489)
      - Student Problems (Box 33, Folder 490)
      - Study of the City (Box 33, Folder 491)
      - Summer Language Institute (Box 34, Folder 492)
      - Summer Programs (Box 34, Folder 493)
      - Summer Term (Box 34, Folder 494)
      - Symphony, Yale (Box 34, Folder 495)
      - Taft, H.D. -- Personal (Box 34, Folder 496)
      - Teacher Preparation Program (Box 34, Folder 497 - 498)
      - Teaching and Learning (Box 34, Folder 499)
      - Teaching Fellows (Box 34, Folder 500)
      - Teaching in the Residential Colleges (Box 34, Folder 501)
      - Teitlebaum, Phyllis (Box 35, Folder 502)
      - Telephone (Box 35, Folder 503)
      - Theater Studies/ Drama (Box 35, Folder 504)
      - Title IX (Box 35, Folder 505)
      - Transcripts, Committee on (Box 35, Folder 506)
      - Transfer Students (Box 35, Folder 507)
      - Treasurer's Office (Box 35, Folder 508)
      - Tribunal, University-wide (Box 35, Folder 509)
      - Tuition (Box 35, Folder 510)
      - Tutoring (Box 35, Folder 511)
      - Undergraduate Organizations, Committee on (Box 35, Folder 512)
      - Visiting Faculty (Box 35, Folder 513)
      - Visiting Faculty Program (Box 35, Folder 514)
      - Wesleyan (Box 35, Folder 515)
      - Writing (Box 35, Folder 517)
      - Writing Courses (Box 35, Folder 518)
      - Yale College Programs of Study (Box 35, Folder 519)
      - Yale College -- Lectures, part-time instructors, acting (Box 35, Folder 520)
    - 1976-1977
      - Administrative Science Major (Box 36, Folder 521)
      - Admissions, Undergraduate (Box 36, Folder 522 - 523)
      - Affirmative Action (Box 36, Folder 524 - 525)
      - Affirmative Action -- Approvals (Box 36, Folder 526)
      - African Studies (Box 36, Folder 527)
      - Afro-American Cultural Center (Box 36, Folder 528)
      - Afro-American Studies Committee (Box 36, Folder 529)
      - Alumni (Box 36, Folder 530)
      - Alumni Journal (Box 36, Folder 531)
      - Alumni Magazine (Box 36, Folder 532)
      - American Council on Education (A.C.E.) (Box 36, Folder 533)
      - American Studies (Box 37, Folder 534)
      - Anthropology (Box 37, Folder 535)
      - Applied Mathematics Committee (Box 37, Folder 536)
      - Applications for Positions (Box 37, Folder 537)
      - Appointments, Junior (Box 37, Folder 538 - 539)
      - Appointments Procedures (Box 37, Folder 540)
      - Appointments, Senior
        - Biological Sciences (Box 37, Folder 541)
        - Committees (Box 37, Folder 542 - 543)
        - Humanities (Box 37, Folder 544)
        - Social Sciences (Box 37, Folder 545)
        - Physical Sciences (Box 38, Folder 546)
      - Architecture (Box 38, Folder 547)
      - Area Studies (Box 38, Folder 548)
      - Art School and Art Major (Box 38, Folder 549)
      - The Association of Colleges in New England (A.C.N.E.) (Box 38, Folder 550)
      - Astronomy (Box 38, Folder 551)
      - Athletics (Box 38, Folder 552)
      - Auditing (Box 38, Folder 553)
      - Band (Box 38, Folder 554)
      - Biology (Box 38, Folder 555)
      - British Studies (Box 38, Folder 556)
      - Budget Committee (Box 38, Folder 557)
      - Bursar (Box 38, Folder 558)
      - Calendar (Box 38, Folder 559)
      - Career Advisory Service (Box 38, Folder 560)
      - Campus Police (Box 38, Folder 561)
      - Chairmanships (Box 39, Folder 563)
      - Chairmen, Departmental (Box 39, Folder 564)
      - Chaplin (Box 39, Folder 565)
      - Chemistry (Box 39, Folder 566)
      - Classics (Box 39, Folder 567)
      - College Council, Yale (Box 39, Folder 568)
      - Combined Science Major (Box 39, Folder 569)
      - Commencement (Box 39, Folder 570)
      - Committees (Box 39, Folder 571)
      - Communications (Box 39, Folder 572)
      - Computer Science (Box 39, Folder 573)
      - Computers at Yale (Box 39, Folder 574)
      - Concilium (Box 39, Folder 575)
      - Consortium on Financing Higher Education (Box 39, Folder 576)
      - Corporation Action (Box 39, Folder 577 - 578)
      - Corporation Minutes (list only) (Box 39, Folder 579)
      - Council of Masters (Box 39, Folder 580)
      - Course Critique (Box 39, Folder 581)
      - Course of Study Committee (Box 40, Folder 582 - 583)
      - Course of Study: Minutes (Box 40, Folder 584)
      - Credits to Departments (Box 40, Folder 585)
      - Davenport (Box 40, Folder 587)
      - Dean Candidates (Box 40, Folder 588)
      - Dean's Annual Report (Box 40, Folder 589)
      - Deans, College (Box 40, Folder 590)
      - Dean's Conferences (Box 40, Folder 591)
      - Deanship, Assistant (Box 41, Folder 592)
      - Dean's Office Staff, 1974-1977 (Box 41, Folder 593)
      - Debating (Box 41, Folder 594)
      - Directors of Undergraduate Study: General (Box 41, Folder 595)
      - Directory, University (Box 41, Folder 596)
      - Distributional Requirements and Guidelines (Box 41, Folder 597)
      - Dramat (Box 41, Folder 598)
      - Drug matters (Box 41, Folder 599)
      - Dwight Hall (Box 41, Folder 600)
      - East Asian Languages and Literatures (Box 41, Folder 601)
      - Economics (Box 41, Folder 602)
      - Editor (Box 41, Folder 603)
      - Engineering and Applied Science (Box 41, Folder 604)
      - English (Box 41, Folder 605)
      - Enrollment, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder 606)
      - Enrollment, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 607)
      - Enrollment, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 608)
      - Executive Committee (Box 42, Folder 609 - 611)
      - Faculty of Yale College (Box 42, Folder 612)
      - Faculty Advising (Box 42, Folder 613)
      - Faculty Handbook (Box 42, Folder 614)
      - Faculty Meetings -- Minutes (Box 43, Folder 615 - 617)
      - Faculty Problems (Box 43, Folder 618)
      - Family Rights and Privacy Act (Box 43, Folder 619)
      - Fanton, Jonathan (Box 43, Folder 620)
      - Fellowships (Box 43, Folder 621)
      - Film Committee (Box 43, Folder 622)
      - Financial Aid (Box 43, Folder 623)
      - Foreign Students (Box 43, Folder 624)
      - French (Box 43, Folder 626)
      - Freshmen (Box 43, Folder 627)
      - Freshmen Counselors (Box 43, Folder 628)
      - Geology and Geophysics (Box 43, Folder 629)
      - German (Box 43, Folder 630)
      - Gifts and Requests (Box 43, Folder 631)
      - Governance (Box 44, Folder 632)
      - Grading, 1975-1977 (Box 44, Folder 633)
      - Graduate school (Box 44, Folder 634)
      - Hatch Prize, Class of 1977 (Box 44, Folder 636)
      - Health Services, Yale (Box 44, Folder 637 - 639)
      - History (Box 44, Folder 640)
      - History of Art (Box 44, Folder 641)
      - History of Science and Medicine (Box 44, Folder 642)
      - Honorary Degrees (Box 44, Folder 643)
      - Honors and Special Projects (Box 44, Folder 644)
      - Housing (Box 45, Folder 645)
      - Human Subjects (Box 45, Folder 646)
      - Humanities, Connecticut Council on (Box 45, Folder 647)
      - Humanities, Council of the (Box 45, Folder 648)
      - Humanities, Interdisciplinary Program in the (Box 45, Folder 649)
      - Humanities, Nat ional Endowment for the (Box 45, Folder 650)
      - Humanities, Special Course in the (Box 45, Folder 651)
      - Hunger Action Project (Box 45, Folder 652)
      - Industrial Relations (Box 45, Folder 653)
      - Information, public (Box 45, Folder 654)
      - Institute for Social and Policy Studies (Box 45, Folder 655)
      - Invitations (Box 45, Folder 656)
      - Italian (Box 45, Folder 657)
      - Japanese Studies (Box 45, Folder 658)
      - Job Opportunities (Box 45, Folder 659 - 661)
      - Joint Committee on Combined B.A.-M.A. Degrees (Box 45, Folder 662)
      - Junior Faculty Fellowships
        - Natural Sciences (Box 45, Folder 663 - 664)
        - Social Sciences (Box 45, Folder 665)
        - Social Sciences (Box 46, Folder 666)
      - Kustow, Michael (Box 46, Folder 668)
      - Languages, Foreign (Box 46, Folder 669)
      - Latin American Studies (Box 46, Folder 670)
      - Law School (Box 46, Folder 671)
      - Leaves of Absence -- Faculty (Box 46, Folder 672)
      - Lecturers, Yale College, Acting Instructors (Box 46, Folder 673)
      - Lecturers -- part-time (Box 46, Folder 674)
      - Lecturers, Yale College -- Acting Instructors, Graduate School Students (Box 46, Folder 675 - 676)
      - Legal Matters (Box 46, Folder 677)
      - Letters, general (Box 46, Folder 678)
      - Library (Box 46, Folder 679)
      - Linguistics (Box 46, Folder 681)
      - Literature Major (Box 46, Folder 682)
      - Mathematics (Box 46, Folder 683)
      - Medical School (Box 46, Folder 684)
      - Minorities, Status of (Box 46, Folder 685)
      - Minorities, Status of (Box 47, Folder 686 - 687)
      - Minority Recruitment (Box 47, Folder 688)
      - M.I.T. Undergraduate Research Opportunity Program (Box 47, Folder 689)
      - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry (Box 47, Folder 690)
      - Morse Proposal (Box 47, Folder 694)
      - Morse Fellowship Committee (Box 47, Folder 695)
      - Morse Proposals (Box 47, Folder 696)
      - Music (Box 47, Folder 697)
      - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures (Box 47, Folder 698)
      - New England Association of Schools and Colleges, Inc. (Box 47, Folder 699)
      - New Haven High Schools Program (Box 47, Folder 700)
      - News Releases (Box 47, Folder 701)
      - National Institute of Education (Box 47, Folder 702)
      - Old Campus (Box 47, Folder 703)
      - Organization and Management, School of (Box 48, Folder 704)
      - Parents' Correspondence (Box 48, Folder 705)
      - Personnel (Box 48, Folder 706)
      - Phi Beta Kappa (Box 48, Folder 707)
      - Philosophy (Box 48, Folder 708)
      - Physics (Box 48, Folder 709)
      - Policy on Proposals, University (Box 48, Folder 710)
      - Political Science (Box 48, Folder 711)
      - Political Union (Box 48, Folder 712)
      - Pre-Medical Advisory (Box 48, Folder 713)
      - Pre-Medical Curriculum of Yale College: A Special Study for the President (Box 48, Folder 714)
      - President's Office (Box 48, Folder 715)
      - Prize Teaching (Box 48, Folder 716)
      - Prize Teaching Fellows (Box 48, Folder 717)
      - Prizes, Undergraduate (Box 48, Folder 718)
      - Programs of Study, Yale College (Y.C.P.S.) (Box 48, Folder 719)
      - PROP (Pre-registration Orientation Program) (Box 48, Folder 720)
      - Provost's Office (Box 48, Folder 721 - 722)
      - Psychology (Box 49, Folder 723)
      - Registrar's Office (Box 49, Folder 724)
      - Religious Studies (Box 49, Folder 725)
      - Research Appointments (Box 49, Folder 726)
      - Resident Fellow Requests (Box 49, Folder 727)
      - ROTC (Box 49, Folder 728)
      - Russian Chorus (Box 49, Folder 729)
      - Russian and East European Studies (Box 49, Folder 730)
      - Safety (Box 49, Folder 731)
      - Scholars of the House (Box 49, Folder 733)
      - Secretary's Office (Box 49, Folder 734)
      - Security (Box 49, Folder 735)
      - Slavic (Box 49, Folder 736)
      - Sociology (Box 49, Folder 737)
      - Spanish (Box 49, Folder 738)
      - Special Students (Box 49, Folder 739)
      - Statistics (Box 49, Folder 740 - 741)
      - Steering Committee (Box 49, Folder 742)
      - Student Letters (Box 49, Folder 743 - 744)
      - Student Problems (Box 49, Folder 745)
      - Summer Language Institute (Box 49, Folder 746)
      - Summer Programs (Box 50, Folder 747)
      - Summer Term (Box 50, Folder 748 - 749)
      - Symphony, Yale (Box 50, Folder 750)
      - Taft, H.D. -- Personal (Box 50, Folder 751)
      - Teacher Preparation (Box 50, Folder 752 - 753)
      - Teaching Fellows (Box 50, Folder 754)
      - Teaching and Learning, Committee on (Box 50, Folder 755 - 756)
        - Teaching Evaluation (Box 50, Folder 757)
      - Teaching Prizes (Box 50, Folder 758)
      - Teaching in the Residential Colleges (Box 51, Folder 759 - 760)
        - Review Committee (Box 51, Folder 761 - 762)
      - Teaching Seminar, Summer (Box 51, Folder 763)
      - Telephone (Box 51, Folder 764)
      - Theater Studies/ Drama (Box 51, Folder 765)
      - Treasurer's Office (Box 51, Folder 766)
      - Tribunal, University-wide (Box 51, Folder 767)
      - Undergraduate Affairs (Box 51, Folder 768)
      - Undergraduate Organizations (Box 51, Folder 769)
      - Undergraduate Organizations Committee (Box 51, Folder 770)
      - University Council (Box 51, Folder 771)
      - Visiting Faculty Program (Box 52, Folder 772)
      - Visitors (Box 52, Folder 773)
      - Women's Affairs (Box 52, Folder 774)
      - Women, Office of the Education of (Box 52, Folder 775 - 776)
    - Restricted
      - Grades, 1971-1972 (Box 53, Folder 777)
      - Prize Teaching Fellowships, 1971-1972 (Box 53, Folder 778)
      - Readmission, 1971-1972 (Box 53, Folder 779)
      - Recommendations, 1971-1972 (Box 53, Folder 780)
      - Salaries and Salary Increase, 1971-1972 (Box 53, Folder 781)
      - Scholarships -- Faculty Children, 1971-1972 (Box 53, Folder 782)
      - Staff Appointments and Promotions (Box 53, Folder 783)
      - Withdrawals, 1971-1972 (Box 53, Folder 784)
      - Letters from Students, 1975-1976 (Box 53, Folder 785)
      - Prize Teaching Applications, 1975-1976 (Box 53, Folder 786 - 787)
      - Recommendations, 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 788)
      - Recommendations, Faculty, 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 789)
      - Personnel Profile Forms, 1976-1977 (Box 54, Folder 790)
      - Recommendations, 1976-1977 (Box 54, Folder 791)